Muslims say that they believe the Bible, but they do not. In fact, they deny that Christ was actually crucified. They refer to him as a prophet because to recognize him as the Son of God would completely invalidate their religion, certainly the Quran.\\n\\nI have friends who are Muslim and I can tell you they do not study the Bible. They only study the Quran, so they only know and believe its teachings.
There are no "rules" for how you hold the racquet.  The physics of the game of tennis will determine the best way to hold it for a particular shot.  As for the backswing, again that doesn't really matter as long as your stroke starts down and goes from low to high.  Without the low to high motion you will not get sufficient lift on the ball to have it carry over the net.  The backswing is just a way to get the racquet to the postistion to start your forward motion to the ball.
The homestead exemption lowers the assessed value of your property up to a maximum of $5,000 as shown in the attached link.  To determine how much that is you need to know the property tax rate where you live.\\n\\nhttp://www.revenue.alabama.gov/advalorem/exemptions/40-9-19.pdf
These are the only dates she has scheduled in the U.S (and Canada) so far for this year.\\n\\nMay\\n20th Nashville, TN Cannery \\n22nd Lawrence, KS Bottleneck \\n23rd Minneapolis, MN Varsity Theatre - Sold Out  \\n24th Milwaukee, WI The Eagles Club  \\n25th Chicago, IL Park West - Sold Out\\n25th Chicago, IL Apple Store Live in store performance.\\n27th Toronto, ONT The Guvernment - Sold Out\\n28th Montreal, QUE Le Tulipe
It's safer than at any store: When you buy online, usually your credit card number is stored in some databases, and only authorized personel with the merchant have access to it. When you show your credit card at the store, any schmuck who works there can steal the number.\\nPlus, most credit cards companies now offer excellent protection to their members for online purchases.
Try Egypt, more friendly and the majority talks English, unlike Syria, the majority talks French.\\nand in any case have a trusted friend from there before you go, friends help and provide security.
Its not a sin to be gay!   just some people read the bible and interperted the meaning of the words to say being an A$$ pirate is a Sin! How ever women are free to go both ways!
Since you already had an e-mail account, go to http://www.friendster.com/ and click sign up wherever you find it.\\n\\nThen type the required information and submit it. Verify your e-mail to start editing profiles and meeting new friends.
The first guideline that I found was:\\n\\n7500 BTU:     150 square feet\\n9000 BTU:     200 square feet\\n10000 BTU:   250 square feet\\n12000 BTU:   350 square feet\\n13000 BTU:   400 square feet\\n\\nSo, 12000 BTU is probably fine.
try  geography...yahoo groups    and  or"Wolf Roder" <Wolf.Roder@uc.edu>
escort
They pop because the pressure is much higher up in the atmosphere, causing the balloon weight to collapse upon itself. They won't make it into space.
well mr.dhoni when u r on the ground or pavilion why do u need to watch it online .
no its defanitly not too late. theres no right age for it. it just has to come naturally on its time ya know?  but i think its just about the greatest feeling ever- thats if its with a person you love.  when its with the person you love,  chills run through my entire body and i feel as light as a feather (a bit corny i know).   but when its with just someone random, i think its kinda gross. it just feels like your wet lips touching his wet lips and its kinda awkard and your minds not really into it.   thats what its like for me at least.      and yeah, your not too late at all, dont worry about it :)
Well, probably a day at the beach now.  The fall and winter are great times for hiking.  But now that's it's warming up, I'll take to the beach!
"Mom, I hate living here and I want to go back to California."\\n\\nShe'll say no, because she moved for MI for a reason.\\n\\nWhen you're 18 and working for a living, you can live anywhere you want. 3 years isn't that long to wait.
I heard on the radio that Conference USA who supplied the refs apologized for many plays. I don't think the refs were doing favortism, they did spot the ball horribly in Iowa's favor twice off by a yard or more. But they did hurt Iowa bad on 5 horrible calls. The refs come from a conferecne that has much slower and smaller players. They could not keep up with the game.
Most girls are going to expect you to spend some time with them. Its unlikely that they are just going to come knocking on your door looking for you. If you are really serious about finding a girlfriend you're going to have to invest some time and actually date. You could try online like Yahoo Personals or meeting people out and about. If you really can't invest the time then just get yourself a prostitute.
Okay, can people that have absolutely no idea stop answering questions on this thing?  It's making a lot of people confused...\\n\\nHere is the full and accurate answer:\\n\\na) greatest number of points obtained in all group matches;\\nb) goal difference in all group matches;\\nc) greatest number of goals scored in all group matches.\\n\\nIf two or more teams are equal on the basis of the above three criteria, their rankings will be determined as follows (this portion has more importance when more than two teams are tied):\\na) greatest number of points obtained in the group matches between the teams concerned;\\nb) goal difference resulting from the group matches between the teams concerned;\\nc) greater number of goals scored in all group matches between the teams concerned;\\n\\nFinal tiebreaker:\\n-Drawing of lots by the Organising Committee for the FIFA World Cup.
Fweigh=mg\\nFweigh= 20kg(9.8)\\nFweigh= 196N\\nFnormal is also 196N\\n\\nFriction= mu(Fnormal)\\nFriction= (.3)(196N)\\nFriction= 58.8N\\n\\nEverytime you see the word "constant speed" or "motionless" that mean all the forces are balanced.\\nSo the Friction="horizonal force"\\nso 58.8 is the horizonal force that keep the object moving at a constant speed.\\n\\nwe have to find acceleration.\\na=Fnet/m\\n\\nFfriction is the Fnet because the horizonal force is romoved\\na=Friction/m\\na= 58.8N/20kg\\na= 2.94m/s^2 (should be -2.94m/s^2 because it is slowing down)\\n\\nVf^2=2ad+Vi^2\\n(0m/s)^2=2(-2.94m/s^2)d+(4m/s)^2\\n-16m^2/s^2= (-5.88m/s^2)d\\nd= 2.72m
It depends on your major.  If it's anything with science, math, engineering, or medical - go for the MA.  If it's Business, Education, or any other field where experience is just as valuable as schooling - wait!  I was able to complete a Master's Degree in a year and a half while working full time.  Again, depending on your major, most universities offer evening and sometimes weekend classes.
http://www.e-frontier.com/article/archive/320/\\nI think they have a tutorial on walking.
well the most expensive gift cost about $30 and it is a birth year coin set
Here's a site where I downloaded most of my mangas.\\n\\nhttp://www.stoptazmo.com/\\n\\nYou can also join the forums there which mainly talk about the hottest manganimes around.\\n\\nHope you're happy~! ^_^
S = C +rC\\n\\nS = (1+r)C\\n\\n1074 = (1 + .6)C\\n\\n1074 = 1.6C\\n\\nC = 671.25
Because us Americans and the British are sick and tired of getting "customer service" from people we can't understand.  It's not discrimination.  If I go to Africa and my Boston accent is not understandable I don't expect Microsoft Africa to make me a phone support technician.\\n\\nI'm just so sick of people using discrimination as an excuse!
Check out wikipedia.org. Type in Greek, and you'll get tons of information.
I don't know how many people I have made happier because someone made me happy, but I do know that I have made myself happy by doing things for others. Even simple things, like loading groceries in a car for an elderly person, and then returning their shopping cart to the collection area, makes me feel happy. It makes me feel like I am putting some good energy out into a world where there's a lot of negativity.\\n\\nI think what you are doing is living the "pass it on" way, and I think the world would be a better place if we could all do it. I try to do it every day, even if it's just the littlest thing, because I think that kindness grows and multiplies and eventually makes the world a better place.\\n\\nAnd kudos to you. You aren't going overboard as long as you aren't starving yourself to do the things you do. What you are doing is passing on your grandparents legacy of love and service to others, and it's a beautiful way to remember them and honor their memory. Doing something for someone of your choosing trumps taking flowers to a gravesite any day.
The same thing that's gonna happen to Mexico when they have to play a good team.  The US are the Concacaf champions, so this pretty much means it's over for any concacaf team.  \\n\\nCongrats czechs, your team played an awesome match.
You can use companies such as Big Idea Group http://www.bigideagroup.net/ as they match up inventors with licensing companies. I've worked with them in the past and they are a reputable company
Check out the NVQ programme through you local adult education college.  You will find that Level 4 will enable you to move forward.  Do that first, then consider doing Level 5, which is an equivalent to a Degree.\\n\\nYou should be able to discuss what you want to do with a careers adviser at the college.
I've never heard of a brusied cervix, I NEVER EVEN HEARD OF THAT DURING CHILD BIRTH.
There are four things that make English Germanic.\\n\\n1)  It's sound system is clearly derived from Proto-Germanic through regular sound changes.  For example, English hound, German Hund (h:h, n:n, d:t); English tide, German Zeit (t:ts; d:t); etc.\\n\\n2)  It's basic vocabulary is clearly Germanic.  For example, (English/German) come/kommen; foot/fuss; five/f³nf; etc.\\n\\n3)  It's grammar is clearly Germanic.  For example, Early Modern English come/comest/cometh, German komme/kommst/kommt; English "i have made", German "ich habe gemacht" (same perfect construction)\\n\\n4)  It's irregularities are the same irregularities found in the other Germanic languages.  For example, English bind/bound, German binden/bund (strong verbs); English man/men, German Mann/Mõnner (vowel change for plural)\\n\\nEnglish is absolutely, 100% a Germanic language through regular sound correspondences, the majority of its basic vocabulary, the majority of its grammatical structures, and the same patterns of irregularity
Thierry Henry without a doubt,mate.
Yahoo is famous for allowing spam in your inbox. Get another email service. I used to get 50 a day. Now that I have GMail I get maybe 2 to 4 a day.
probably the shadow puppets... with all of that "complex shadow puppet" generating, there would have to be some trapezius muscle development, right? and three to four could be naptime.
just lower the screen resolotion and the ingame resolution and everything will work, remember it's the fault of the game and not your computer, so it's the game which dose not fit the requirments.
Do NOT Download - its a EXE file - a program\\n\\nI have just reported it
For the wedding cake you can use the flake fish food and stack it, wet it, let it dry, and the serve it to them, however for the honey moon you'll want to go with the pellets that last a few days so that they can be alone on their honeymoon\\nCongratulations
Do u think Indians would support their PM if he chose to attack the US? Or the Chinese if they decided to take Alaska? Bush is absolutely opportunistic. More so Jeb and Cheney. Iran in fact, should be made out as a case for peace. All US is doing is depleting oil reserves of Middle east so that one day the world would be dependent on Texas and Alaska. Then the east would attack US for the same reasons... \\n\\nSo summary: NO, the US of A should NOT attack Iran.
The movie was decent but had several pitfalls. It takes over an hour before you see Kong. The action sequences are significently longer then they need to be. Jackson went way longer then he needed to. \\n\\nYou probably want to wait till they are 14 or 15. The scenes with the natives are pretty dicey and can easily scare young teenagers. Also, there are a bunch of scenes that are startling including dinosaurs and massive insects. \\n\\nBut for all its action, it does have a connection between naomi Watts (sp?) and Kong that you don't see in most action films. My ex-girlfriend actually started crying when they starting to strafe Kong. \\n\\nAlso Jack Black doesn't say or do anything funny in the movie whatsoever. That was a let down. \\n\\nGive it a year or two before showing them and be willing to sit down for 3+ hours.
Love is the best emotion that God has given us! I don't know if you believe this, but its written that God is love, and we are made in his image......so when we love we are actually doing something that God does too!\\nWhen we are love a special someone its the most beautiful thing in the world! We have a capacity to love different people and things! I love being in love!\\n\\nThanks for the love...ly question!
Wow.  Scary.  From what you said it does sound suspicious.  I'd first talk to any relatives/her friends (hopefully in confidence) to see if they have noticed anything.  If so, do an intervention. There are mediators for that.  Ask a church leader or a private org like narcotic or alcoholics annonymous.  I'd do all that before getting authorities involved - that would be a last resort.\\n\\nDon't give up and never ever blame yourself. Children of drug/alcohol abusers often do.  DOn't fall into that trap.\\n\\nBest wishes to you.  Be strong.
OK... let's see all your options.\\nTo work in the USA you either need a work visa or a green card.\\nWork visa will give you the right to work for a limited amount of time, while with a green card you can live and work in the USA basically for ever.\\nFor a work visa, you need a company to sponsor you. For a green card, you can get one with a company's sponsorship, with the 'green card lottery' aka diversity visa, serving in the military or marrying an american.\\nUsually, it's hard to get sponsorship for a green card by an american company. It's expensive and takes a lot of time (1-5 years). Usually, you come on a work visa, and while you're on a work visa, you do the green card at the same time.\\nThere are several types of work visas. The easiest to get is the J1, which is for an 'internship' or 'stage'. It costs around $500 to do and can be obtained in a couple of weeks. It is valid for up to 18 months. H1B is harder to obtain, but it can last for up to 6 years. Usually you need a degree or a specialization to obtain one. \\nYou can do the visa papers yourself, but there are agencies and lawyers that can do the paperwork for you (if you pay them, of course).
Go on to the mets website and search game-used stuff. I am 99% sure that they will have the size and make of his glove.
Typing in all caps is the online equivalent to yelling, and therefore bad manners. All caps are also harder to read. Here's why...\\n\\nOnce we have mastered reading (not sounding out words letter by letter), we recognize words by their shape rather than by the order of the letters. Think about it...you read whole words, not individual letters. When words are typed in all caps, they lose their shape -- that is, they become rectangular. The reader has to revert to reading them one letter at a time, hence slowing them down.\\n\\nGraphics designers use this as a tool to draw attention by slowing down a reader. It is an effective tool when used properly.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH BIN LADEN!!  With every poll showing majorities of Americans both fed up with Bush's war against Iraq and convinced that Bush's invasion of Iraq has made Americans less safe, the White House moron proposes to start another war by attacking Iran. VP Cheney has already ordered the U.S. Strategic Command come up with plans to strike Iran with tactical nuclear weapons.The Bush administration is insane. If the American people do not decapitate it by demanding Bush's impeachment, the Bush administration will bring about Armageddon. This may please some Christian evangelicals conned by Rapture predictions, but World War III will please no one else.What few people today actually discuss is this; just how bad would it be if Iran manages in a few years to create a primitive nuclear weapon or two? Iran has nuclear powers Pakistan and India to its east, and a hostile nuclear Israel to its west. Israel has more nuclear weapons per capita than any nation in the world, and any reading of her history suggests she would not be loath to use them if she felt threatened. Iran's leaders are mean screwballs these days, but not insane; any leader of Iran would know that Israel would destroy their nation and their people should they ever attempt to lob a creaky rivet-popping missile with a warhead of any kind towards Tel Aviv. As to any presumed danger that those nutty Persians will hand over little nukes to "terrorists"--there are a whole bunch of nations right now who are perfectly capable of doing so anyway. Oh, and by the way, how does the nation with the largest nuclear force of all time, who is the only one in history who has used these weapons, whose current mean and somewhat screwball leaders talk of using "tactical" nuclear weapons in their already illegal wars--how does that nation become the one to decide who else gets to join their dandy little club? I say, to our  both parties, lighten up. Iran isn't going to nuke Miami anytime soon.
I know it!!! It wasn't a film exactly. It was Autopsy with Dr. Baden. I think Autopsy 6??? But there was Someone Von Cosel who treated this girl, she died, he was in love, yada yada yada, you remembered the story pretty well. I hope this helps.
Try to divert his attention from his interests with books that interest him.  Develop the habit of reading that way.  Also be a friend to him and keep discussing subjects that interests him and taken his confidence and then slowly direct his attention to his studies.
Probably referring to the fact that you see each other less and less and eventually it could become once a year; you also could have mis-heard him.  The more you dwell on these kind of things the worse it seems- you should have called him soon after and laughed, saying "See you next year?! Very funny!".  That would have broken the ice- you can still do this if it hasn't been too long...
i find myself in an ideal position to answer this question.\\n\\nRecently me and my girlfriend had split up. We had been having sex while dating and now since we've broken up, we've decided that as long as we're single, we should enjoy the occasional sex (which is becoming more and more frequent). Most people will tell yo that to have sex you must be committed and it should be for love blah blah blah... \\nI say this, if you both enjoy it and you both understand the rules, WHY NOT?
because Bush has moral values. No one knew what Kerry stood for. He couldn't make up his mind.
I started playing a few games starting with the Age of Empire series, because I was fascinated by the ability to move those little guys to cut trees, collect berries and mining.  The fighting part was OK, but it seems that it required speed, hot keys and just overwhelming opponents with number.\\nI am playing Total War Rome now.  It is still fun.  Even though I miss the little guys doing chores, I found the cinematic fighting scenes are much better.  It is like watching a movie.  The fighting technique is much different.\\nGive it a try and you might even find more people to play with on line.
Those are 2 good ideas you mentioned (the snowman and the cookies)...I had to this years ago when I was on the volleyball team... I made homemade cards with some new greeting each time I put one in their locker (you can do it on your comp if you have a printer) and taped Christmas candies to them. You can also go to a dollar store and get a small stocking and fill it with $1 items that the person may like or find cute...like pencils and pens and stuff like that. There's all kinds of stuff...just use your imagination.....GOOD LUCK!!
To protest the governments inaction on the price of gas, yes. It is actually needed to get the attention of the people in charge. If solidarity was displayed then it would work, yes I would participate.
its not just "homeschooled" its being homeschooled i've been homeschooled all my life and i'm dying to go to  highschool i'm in the 10th grade...unless your parents have the time and are willing to theres no chance...ask them see what they say.. being homechooled isn't a peice of cake
You think that your vote means something..  The elections are very subtly fixed by popularity votes and dumping money into programs that affect the popularity of one candidate over another.  It is a fantasy to think that you have very much control over who governs you.  The political system knows its limits and is very controlled.  They want the people half way peaceful and working.  You either vote democrat or republican, anything else is throwing away your vote.  What if you don't like either??  There are no options.\\nMany said because people are lazy, but I believe that folks in general have completely lost faith that they have any say in the Govt.  Their votes don't matter any more.
don't be wearing thick cotton athletic socks if that is what you have! They absorb sweat, then they start to chafe...and pretty soon you are either blistered or rubbed raw.\\n\\nGo to your running store and buy thin socks (short on the ankle, usually some design or something on em, and about $6 or $7 a pair) and wear those.\\n\\nCheck out this site, it shows the type of sock I am talking about...these are a little more expensive than I like, but they are exactly the size and material:\\n\\nhttp://www.swimoutlet.com/Triathlong_Socks_s/540.htm\\n\\nRe the blister...take it easy till it goes down. Sometimes if they are small i pop them and wrap them...but bigger ones just need time...
First thing if you want an answer in joules, a joule is a Nm, you you must convert the 2.00km into 2000m by multiplying by 1000.\\n\\nw= Fd\\nw= 5.60102N X 2000m\\nw= 11202.06J\\n\\nThe work done on the tugboat was 11202.06 J.
Essentially, this view is based on the fact that the two States have their nominating processes (the Iowa caucuses and New Hampshire primary) at the very beginning. Candidates want to make a good showing here in order to demonstrate that they are viable within their own party. However, I feel it's overstating the case to say they "choose.....with limited input"  Recent campaigns have not borne that idea out. Voters in New Hampshire and Iowa do not, as a rule, represent opinions and concerns of the rest of the country.\\n\\nViewed as a horse race, which is how the media cover campaigns and elections, these two States do have an inordinate amount of attention paid to them, again only because they come first in the cycle-------they're the only show in town in the early stages. Most years, they're quickly forgotten once the next round of primaries come along.\\n\\nThinking back, the last time I remember these States  having real impact was in 1968, when Eugene McCarthy got 42% of the N.H. vote in the Democratic Primary to LBJ's 58%, but that was enough of a shocker to cause LBJ to take his hat out of the ring.\\n\\nThe reality is,not the early state contests but the wheeling and dealing that bring the foregone results at the National Conventions. You have to go back 46 years, to 1960, to see a Convention where the outcome was in any doubt.
It's called Fascism..... it was huge in Europe in the 1940's.\\n\\nPersonally, I think it's best that Iran doesn't aquire nukes.....\\n\\nSome leaders will use them without thinking of the consequences.\\n\\nPS.\\n\\nThere seems to be a lot of people on here who are under the illusion that most of the anti-US feeling from other countries is unwaranted. Some of the hatred towards the US stems from US foreign policy and activites of the CIA but most of it begins with resentment towards the corporations like Coca-cola, McDonalds and the large financial and mineral corporations. Some countries are seriously affraid for their culture and their freedom.  They  have a very real concern about the "infection" of Americanisation in their society.\\n\\nThat is the reason why so many countries want to arm themselves with nukes. In the middle East there is growing resentment and hatred towards the US. Threats like " The use of Military force has not been ruled out" do not help to calm countries like Iran and Syria and  do not lead them to beleive the US to be friendly. \\n\\nIf you combine these factors with zealous, hateful teachings that bear no relationship to the teachings of the Qur'an being aggressively promoted by maniacs on a power trip. These feed off the fears of decent people and the change in them begins. \\n\\nIt's very easy for a lot of people to blame the US directly for their problems. A large ammount of problems in the third world ARE the fault of US corporations and Government. It comes down to the individual to not accept or indulge in the things on offer from the US.\\n\\nMy point is that the US is becoming an Empire and in doing so they are provoking very dangerous people. Empires grow and consume other other organisations and societies. They deplete their resources, violate their people and their culture and turn the people in to slaves. Would you want that done to your own country? How would it feel to have Taliban troops walking down your street kicking in the doors, needlessly violating, torturing and killing the occupants (you, you neighbours, your children)? Would that make you feel welcoming towards them or would you fight back? you would fight back becaause even the most peace loving among you would not be able to bear what you see.\\n\\nRealistically, people look for an answer in desperate times and that is most likely to involve religion - that is the same globally.\\nAny religion in the world promotes peace. So when people adhere to a faith and something American starts to interfere with their faith...porn, Hollywood films, drugs, alcohol, western unmodest fashion etc. the psychological association is there that the US is evil, promoting all these obscene things to tempt people away from God and their faith. Anybody in that situation would be hostile. Add the fear of invasion and that's when terrorism begins. Those people believe they have a very realistic reason to seek WMD's. The problem is that they get carried away with the whole idea that they are good and the US is evil. They then forget to question whether their own actions are right or wrong. \\n\\nTheir countries are also run by politicians who are greedy liars just the same as all of our politicians are. They manipulate their people through the media as well. They promote the anti-US feeling to the people. Before you know it there is a very clear and present danger to the American way of life and that has to be preserved which may involve aggressive military action against a whole group of countries and organisations that are hostile to the US....which, to apply a catchy name to group the whole lot together with out actually directly blaming any of them: we could call them something like the Axis of Evil for example.\\n\\nSee at this point  a whole load of false ideas have destroyed peoples ability to think rationally on all sides. \\n\\nAt this point your Government seeks to eradicate any external threats and in fear of 
It is a violation of the Fair Credit Reporting Act to access credit without consent, barring criminal investigation under warrant.  Every time, however, that your credit is checked, it is required for the credit center to send you written notification of your credit check.\\n\\nIt is not discrimination, however.  People use that word way too much, and use it incorrectly.  It is discrimination if no one else in the office experienced the credit check, and there is something that differentiates you from others in the office that is covered under federal and state laws.\\n\\nIt is illegal and punishable not only under criminal action but also civil action.
I can only see success for him. While hitters, with the exception of Hideki Matsui, are not as powerful in the US, the pitchers seem to be able to adapt to the MLB easier. He has some filthy stuff and I will draft him on several fantasy leagues next year.
I agree with huggy and also the people who are telling you that 28 pounds is WAY too much weight for you to lose.  I know you are on the shorter side, but 80 pounds is still too thin for you.  You should talk to your parent(s) about going to see a doctor, and have your doctor tell you what a good weight for you is.  Then you can think about getting your buddy.\\n\\nAn in-person buddy is much better for this kind of thing - someone who can get together and exercise with you, hold you accountable for eating good things, you can learn how to cook healthy together, etc.  Maybe your school nurse or counselor can put you in touch with a good buddy "candidate."\\n\\nMarina, listen:  Junior high is a scary place, and some people there are at the height of meanness.  You could go in to junior high weighing 19  pounds, and someone will still call you FAT.  Getting down to a certain weight is NOT going to protect your heart and soul from the mean people in your life.  The people who are mean will find something to insult you for, true or false.\\n\\nThe trick you have to learn has nothing to do with weight loss.  You have to learn how to block those mean comments out of your brain, to not let them in and not let them bother you.  Find a friend in your life - in person - to stick close to and support you when you get to junior high, and start practicing now how to ignore the people who call you fat, ugly, stupid, whatever.  Those people are worthless, and their comments have no value unless you give them value by allowing them to change YOUR behavior.  If you let those haters hurt your feelings, and let them make you think you need to weigh 80 pounds, then they win.  Don't let that happen.
Yes your vote counts--the last two presidential elections have proven that.\\n\\nBut remember, it's not just presidential elections.  There are local elections where your vote counts even more.   \\n\\nAnd if you live in Cook County, Illinois, your vote counts as often as you vote !  :)
Yes.  I fell in love at first sight... 5 years after I met my DH...\\n\\nAs for "how do I know for sure it will last?"  Well, love is a commitment.  It lasts if you DECIDE it will last.  Infatuation will come and go, but love last if you are committed to loving and being with someone the rest of you life.
They are jealous.\\nThey wish they could be as good as The Yankees always are.
The size of the monitor is secondary to the resolution of the monitor. Make sure that the 15 inch monitor has the same resolution as the 17inch that you're using to author pages. Also, in Front Page 2000 and up, you can set the resolution of the 'output' page to whatever you like. If your 15inch monitor isn't capable of displaying, say 1024x768, you'll have to adjust the 17inch down to 800x600 for example. Don't forget to ajust the Front Page setting to match.
I think you're right. Most Christian boycotters are very selective in who they boycott. Homosexuality is one "hot spot."\\n\\nTo be honest, if they boycott every company that had a disagreement with their theology, they couldn't buy anything at all. They should be living somewhere in hovels, without power, clothes, and food.\\n\\nIn any case, our job is to be salt in the world, not constantly protest what the world is doing.\\n\\nIf they are so worried about homosexuality, they would do much better being friends with homosexuals, finding out their needs, and serving them as real people whom they cared about, instead of impersonally fighting to simply take things away from them that they really do need.
in fact i look nothing like it....there are NO fat 52 year old avatars available
planet dan - the Bible very specifically says that the slave is "PROPERTY."  It says that if a slave owner beats his slave so badly that the slave goes unconcious for days, but then wakes up, the owner receives NO punishment for, "he is his property."\\n\\nFor those of you believe that the New Testament nullifies all this, I do not understand how you make sense of the fact that God ever gave this law in the first place!  Was God cruel in "Old Testament" times?  Did he suddenly have a change of heart 2000 years ago?\\n\\nAnd saying the Buddhist faith is lazy is about the most inaccurate thing I have ever heard.  Buddhists meditate and this is NO easy task.  In fact, it is probably the most difficult thing, to gain control of one's mind and to work on their own inner traits and become more compassionate and good people without the negative traits of anger, etc.\\n\\nBuddhism is hard work, but it is worth every bit of it.
You could go out and buy a RAM chip or maybe buy a better processor for your computer. But you have to check if your motherboard is compatible with them before buying it.
I know this is a joke........................to marry ...........the other party has to say I do.....................do you think a fox can understand.........I want you to think over the question you ask ..........and get real with life...............................and that is not a joke
My family sounds just like your family. It's frustraoccasionallybe very upsetting. I just refuse to discuss any ones weight with them at all and I shut down any weight conversations they attempt with me - positive or negative - because I figure that if I seek their approval I also invite them to criticise.\\n\\nTo answer the other part of your question - I have occassionally been known to comment on people's weight. BUt only when it is positive such as, someone who has been trying to lose weight and has been successful.
Blow them off, their obviously not making the effort to keep the friendship going, so put it in their hands.  If they want to contact you they will.
We don't know when exactly when Jesus was born(could be the summer) and that case even the year. The bible is not persice when it comes to this matter so the do the early christian leaders do was genius. They want to mark a specific date to rebemer Jesus birth and they want to convert people aslo so.  So they pick a roman pagan holiday that was at the end of each year and replace it with the christain holiday christmas.  Christanity is very flexable at incorparting new thing to convert people. How do you thing the Christmas tree got started?
Three men.
you have been open with her that you do not want her attention.  you might let your husband know about it so he is aware of what happened but not push it further.  she most likely will leave you alone from now on, give it a chance. if she doesnt, stay away from where she is going to be if she makes you uncomfortable.
Can try LENOVO.If looking for cheaper one try Compaq(Athlon processor).If want a good one,try IBM Thinkpad
It depends on the jurisdiction. Each legislative body makes its own rules about what needs to be published and how and when. All federal laws are published by the Government Printing Office and are also online at http://thomas.loc.gov Administrative decisions are not as regulated, but are a matter of public record, so if you request them, you can see any information about them. Executive appointments requiring Senate oversight are published by the GPO and online as well as part of the Congressional record. As for state and local publications, there are too many and they are too different to make any generalizations. See the legislature's website.
I think it varies.  I had morning sickness right off the bat, but my friend never had morning sickness.  I also had it worse at night - don't know why it's called morning sickness.  Eat crackers before getting out of bed.
I'm 38, and yes I am also sex crazy,I don't care about the snuggling as much as I just want to get f*cked. I love my husband and every aspect of our sex life. I also satisfy myself w/ toys while home alone about 3-4 days a week, as well as get my husband at least 2-3 times a week, mostly 2-3 times on the weekend.  I know I still could fit another guy into my routine, that's how much sex I need right now and for the past 3 years at least. It freaks me out to be like this though, you too?
get one of those fog horns like they take yo ball games......next time he starts.....go outside and blow it til he shuts up.....do it every time......and when fat butt asks what the hell....tell her it sounds better to you than her kids caterwauling.
I could give you all kinds of suggestions, however, I think the best thing you can do is go to a local department store to the sport section. Talk to an associate that knows a lot about fishing. They will be able to help you one on one better. They will be able to show you what kinds of things to get that suits the area you live in and what kind of fish are caught there. \\n\\nAs far as a gift "basket", I would say no. Go with a fishing vest and place the things in the vest that you are going to buy for him. Plus a nice fishing hat.\\n\\nHope I helped....Good luck!!
depreciation is related to wear and value \\nthat is why land does not depreciate\\nand why depreciation is based on the useful life of the asset\\n\\n(I see that irish copied the def from the wiki, which I often do, but in this case the definition is not entirely correct.)
Manatees are friends of Dragon, so Dragon would go over and say hi. :)
I read an article in a TIME magazine featuring three important people........ Einstein, Freud, and Karl Marx (the founder of Communism.) Do some reseach on Karl Marx, his ideas are great.\\n\\nI too like some of the ideas of Communism (in theory).  But unfortunately, many cruel dictators throughout history have ruined the idea of communism and given it a bad name.  So many people in the US will dislike you for even saying that you like the concept.  I remember my great grandmother totally tripping out on "The Commies." lol\\n\\nGood luck and keep an open mind!
